this is the time known as the great pirate era a countless array of pirates go to battle across
the seas in search of the one piece the legendary treasure left behind by gold watcher king of the
pirates monkey d luffy a boy whose body turned to rubber after eating the gum gum fruit set sail to
become the next king of the pirates as luffy and his crew conquer numerous obstacles they capture
the unwanted attention of the world government which will use any means necessary to stop them
can't wait to see what kind of adventures up next with a charted course washing danger and intrigue
the crew will cut a path across the grand line to the new world
separated from his crew luffy and his newfound cohorts have hijacked a navy ship in order
to rescue his brother ace who's been transported to navy hq for execution screw you nobody is that
crazy surely you guys heard about the war brewing between white beard and the navy uh war navy
headquarters well we passed through the gate of justice isn't that right our destination is any's
lobby or navy hq this tub current is restricted to government passage only it's one giant whirlpool
that connects the government's three major facilities
that's enough don't get too flashy you guys are high on power and acting impulsively
so listen i want all of you to live out a dream with me for today i'll conquer white beard and thus rule the world
all right then now let's win this war you guys to navy hq
so i guess the mutiny's over
let them have fun while they can
the friends whereabouts the waveria report and the cyborg animals
oh
uh
Huh?
I know you're worried about Ace, but standing vigil won't help.
You should rest and prepare yourself for the battle.
The war that approaches us will be a trying one and one that changes the tide of the times.
Having just escaped from the greatest prison in the world, we may take heart, but the fortress
that lies before us is ever more imposing.
Far away, but not long ago, on a sky island known as Witheria, a weather wizard, or rather
a weather scientist, continued his studies.
Hey, hey, hey, young lady!
Hey, hey!
Hey, hey, hey!
Young lady!
Hey!
Yes, hey!
What do you want now?
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey,
young lady!
Hey!
Yes, hey! What do you want now?
Oh, my face! What is this thing?
Why, it's my famous cloud candy, of course.
Well, I suppose it's not famous yet.
It's taken many hours of research
to get it tasted like cotton candy, you know.
But I think it's all been worth it, don't you?
Don't stick it up! Get it, get it, get it!
Are you nuts?
Violence won't do, young lady. Let's just calm down.
I could have died.
Oh, wow, that does taste like cotton candy.
Yeah, weren't you listening?
Wow, really is an island of wonders.
Hey, I'm just checking.
But are you positive we're still heading
to the Saba Odi Archipelago?
Of course.
I said I would grant you a favor, and I meant it.
Okay, but it was quite a long time ago
when you told me that.
Not to be rude, but when will we get there?
Huh? What do you mean?
Hmm?
Ah! When do we get there?
Impossible to say, since Laveria travels on the winds.
So, if the typhoon hits, we'll get there pretty fast.
Then how far did we get yesterday?
My guess is about 600 feet or so.
Seriously. If this stupid island wasn't floating in the sky,
I would have bailed already.
That's silly. Even if we were on land,
you'd still be too far away for it to do any good.
If you stay here, you'll get there someday, at least.
I know, but I'm not going there for a vacation.
This is urgent business, okay?
Hmm. We could go down for a bit.
Frankly, I could stand to stock up on some funding for my research.
Huh?
Go down where?
On the ground.
You can do that?
My research is actually quite costly.
Thankfully, my weather expertise is valuable to the land dwellers,
so I can turn a profit pretty handily.
What is this?
Young lady!
Over here!
A ship?
Whoa!
What the heck?
It flies?
Whoa!
No!
Here we go!
Huh?
Whoa!
What's the island I was looking for?
Oh...
that's the island I was looking for!
Let's land there!
Oh...
It's so dry.
Wow, that's rough.
You can save our island, and we're to believe that?
Why not? Your problem is straightforward enough, I think.
Just a bit of rain should set things right in no time.
Thankfully, I'm an expert with the weather.
I'll gladly summon a shower or two.
You jest.
So how about we make a little deal?
Does a hundred million berries sound fair?
That's a lot!
Alas, even for the rain, it's too much.
Did I highball it a bit?
Are you kidding me? Do they look rich to you?
I see.
Well, how does a hundred sound?
So cheap!
You've got some pretty awful business sense, old man.
It's fine.
That aside, can you really do this?
Aren't you being a bit optimistic?
Just watch and believe, my dear lady.
This will be easy.
What's that?
Soap bubbles, maybe?
Looks like there's something inside.
One more thing.
Could you take this and generate some wind for me, please?
Oh, I see.
Do you want it full power?
But of course!
No!
D définis.
Oh, rain clouds.
How could that be?
It's raining!
Yeah!
What did I tell you?
They sure are happy, aren't they?
A science of weather has many wonderful applications.
Well, I suppose this is goodbye, young lady.
I already spoke with the mayor about your journey.
He said he would be happy to help you along the way.
I'm not going.
Why not?
It's obvious, isn't it?
Because I want to learn this science of yours.
I'm pretty impressed.
Really?
Since it's still a while to Saba Odi, would you mind teaching me along the way?
I'd be thrilled.
Great.
I can't wait.
Anyone with a passion for the weather is welcome to learn from me.
There's still one left.
Perfect.
Now, look.
This here is what we in the business call a soap bubble thundercloud.
Whoa!
That's not good at all.
What are you doing?
You old fool.
Science exacts a price on its learner, my dear.
I'll exact a price out of you.
Help.
Help us old.
This is the Mechanical Island Futureland Baltimore, also known as the birthplace of the genius.
Super relaxed.
Aw, man.
He was so much fun before and now he's just late.
Grandpa, tell me you have a plan.
We've got to turn Frankie back somehow.
I ordered some cola for him, but it hasn't arrived yet.
I'm afraid he's beyond our help without him.
I'm sure a bottle or two will bring him back to his preferred old, uh, I mean charming old self.
But we can't make him go wild.
Or can we?
It's cold.
How on earth did I end up out here in the elements?
Huh?
Ah.
How lovely.
A scarf for me.
Thanks.
Oh my, oh my, oh my, oh my, oh my, oh my, oh my, oh my.
Goodness.
This, this is a nightmare.
Huh?
Keep out.
This is an enclosed forest of mechanical animals.
This is an怪しい monocorn, the
due to fireNEcar n Ami.
Guide to the freebolts of mechanical animals,
which means help us نures up.
This is deadly and ugly.
This is unstable technology,
which means he's scared by Одержа and Aeroора Angels.
Which means he's scared by stormwater tom겠습니다.
This is singular harmony when he has utterly out a jean.
Dedicated by stormwater dreamers.
And this is brutal.
That is redemption.
Isn't this painful,
yes,
we can't MIKE OSCE.
Ready for plan A, surprise awakening in the jungle.
Nothing's more wild than mecha animals.
This will get him back on track for sure.
Don't try this at home, kids.
Now, now, let's calm down, shall we, friends?
Because you seem agitated this morning.
Did you remember to eat your breakfast?
It is the most important meal of the day, you know.
Let's work on getting those blood sugar levels up.
Huh? Hold on a second.
That means it's breakfast time for me, too.
Ah, you silly goose.
Delicious.
No better way to start the day than with a cup of tea.
Would you care for some tea, too?
Let's cherish every moment, friends.
Aw, it's not working.
Someone help us!
Ah!
Ah! My friends! Good day!
It's Frankie!
That's not proper!
How about Mr. Frank from now on?
Mm-mm, violence is never the...
I know you're at an age where you want to be naughty.
But listen...
We can sort this out...
No!
Like gentlemen!
Nothing...
Good...
Ever comes!
Awful violence!
Come on, just fight back!
Please!
You can't reason with gorillas!
Relax!
Listen to words...
Listen to what I have to...
If you'd let me talk...
I have the...
Wisdom to impart...
No!
My friend...
We must...
Not...
We...
Ah!
Huh?
Whoa!
Yeah!
Oh, yeah!
Oh!
Super!
What do you think I am, you punks?
Chopped liver?
You can't step to Frankie!
He's back!
You are seriously starting to scare me!
Oh, yeah!
Wow!
What's wrong?
I cooled off a bit and ran out of steam.
Literally.
Huh?
You mean, you're gonna turn back?
No!
I know just the place to go!
Where are you taking me, kid?
To the house of Dr. Vegapunk.
It's not far, and I bet we can find a machine that makes cola there.
Say what now?
Baltimore's famous for its technology,
and this guy is the genius that cooked up a whole ton of it.
Like all those mechanical animals you just fought
were made by Dr. Vegapunk ages ago.
I heard he was kind of an oddball,
and he did leave the island overrun with dangerous cyborgs,
but that doesn't make it any less of a genius.
My grandpa told me there's some dangerous stuff in there,
but it's an emergency, and I have you to protect me,
so it should be okay.
What're I doing?
Will I come here?
All right.
legenor.
Let's see.
This is not good.
I'm going to be king of the pirates.
Let's see.